{
    "subject": "resource/Angel_Blue",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/isPrimaryTopicOf",
    "object": "http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Angel_Blue",
    "human_readable": "Angel Blue is primarily about http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Angel_Blue.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9151415824890137,
            "question": "What is Angel Blue primarily about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8814140558242798,
            "question": "Is there a Wikipedia page for Angel Blue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.844426155090332,
            "question": "What is the URL of the Angel Blue Wikipedia page?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7756364345550537,
            "question": "How can I access the Wikipedia page for Angel Blue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7561452388763428,
            "question": "What kind of information can I find on the Angel Blue Wikipedia page?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7527815699577332,
            "question": "What topics are likely covered on the Angel Blue Wikipedia page?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7195209264755249,
            "question": "Who or what is associated with Angel Blue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6955565214157104,
            "question": "Is there any other information you have about Angel Blue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6051770448684692,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Angel Blue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5999825596809387,
            "question": "Is Angel Blue a person, place, or thing?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Angel Blue is primarily about http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Angel_Blue.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1906_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Angel Blue?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1906_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any other information you have about Angel Blue?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1906_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who or what is associated with Angel Blue?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1906_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1906_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1906_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1906_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1906_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1906_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1906_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1906_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1906_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1906_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1906_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe query \"Angel Blue is primarily about http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Angel_Blue\" is supported by the documents, which provide information about Angel Blue's career as a soprano, her origins, and details of her performances."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "It's a completely different person with the same name.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}